哟 哟 继续放
Yo, yo! Turn that back on.
继续放!
Put it back on!
别看着我 你知道不是我干的
Don't look at me, 'cause you know I didn't do it.
我告诉过你 你最好换上新电池了
Hey, you better have put fresh batteries in that thing,,like I told you.
我换了 中士 你给我的时候 就换上了
I did, sarge, right when you--when you gave it to me, I-I did.
我放进去了
I put 'em in.
那拍一下试试看
Well, then, hit it or something.
要不然你们就只能听我唱歌了!
Otherwise, y'all are gonna have to listen to me sing!
不要慌 不要对我们开枪,还有不要死
Don't panic.Don't shoot us,and n't diE.
明白了吗 阿G?
You got it, g?
该干活了
Up and at 'em.
你应该在出门诊才对
You're supposed to be in clinic duty.
下面哭声 咳嗽声 我难道能睡着
Yeah, like I can sleep down there with all the crying and coughing.
这里 退伍海军陆战队员,觉得自己得了海湾战争综合症
Here.Ex-marine.Thinks he has gulf war syndrome.
没有这码子病的
There's no such thing.
有人这么告诉他
So he's been told.
可他还是有无法解释的,心智衰弱 皮疹 以及关节疼痛
It hasn't stopped the unexplained fatigue, rashes, and joint pain.
你还得知道 他是医院一个捐助人的侄子
And just so you know, he's the nephew of a benefactor I owe a favor,
所以不管你愿不愿意 你都得接下这件病例
so you're gonna take this case whether you like it or not.
我为什么会不愿意?
Why wouldn't I want to take the case?
这家伙又累又痛
The guy's tired and sore.
这可是我的最爱--
It's gonna be chapter one in my--
不要慌 不要对我们开枪,还有不要死
don't panic. Don't shoot us, and don't die.
你认识他?
You know him?
这辈子从来没见过
Never met him beforein my life.
那好吧 你就快见到了
Okay, well, you're about to.
他在过来的路上
He's on his way here.
起身召集你的团队吧 你有活要干了
Get your ass up and get your team together.,You have work to do.
-=怪杰医生豪斯=-,第三季 第16集,"最高机密"; "Top Secret"
House.M.D,Season 3 Episode 16
太奇妙了
That's amazing.
才不是
No, it's not.
不是?
It's not?
我能用鼻子吹口琴,从小孩儿耳朵里掏出硬币...
I can play the harmonica with my nose, make a penny come out of a child's ear--
或者从别的孔也行...
or any other orifice, for that matter--
还有 在某种条件下,同时让两个女人迷恋我
and, given the right circumstances,,can bring two women to simultaneous ecstasy.
这条件就是指 她们两人协商好,从你同一张信用卡里扣钱
The right circumstances being their agreement,to bill you on the same credit card.
而我绝对做不到,梦见一个素未谋面的人
And what I absolutely cannot do is dream about,someone I've never seen before.
你理解不了 可不代表不可能发生
Well, just because you don't understand it doesn't mean it can't happen.
不可能发生就是不可能!
True...it can't happen because it can't happen!
也许你梦到的并不是特定的他
Well, maybe you didn't dream about this guy specifically.
是啊 一个长得和他一摸一样的家伙
Right, just some other guy who looks exactly like him.
不 你想象了一个普通海军陆战员
No, you imagined some generic marine,
你看见照片后 把他的脸代入了进去
then you placed his face in the dream after you saw the picture.
Sort of a coincidence mixed with a little d閖vu.
一点巧合加一点似曾相识
他从来没有来过这家医院
there's no record of him ever coming into the clinic.
我肯定以前在别的地方见过他
So I must have seen him before somewhere else.
你们当童子军的时候认识的
Fine, you've known him since cub scouts.
有意思的问题不是做梦的内容 而是缘由
A more interesting question isn't what you dreamed, but why?
我猜你要不就是渴望和你爸爸重归于好...
I'm guessing you're longing for either a renewed relationship with your dad...
要不就是想发展一段同志新关系
or a new relationship with one of the village people.
他是海军 而不是海军陆战队的
He was in the navy, not the marines.
我以为你爸爸是海军陆战队的
I thought your dad was in the marines.
村民乐团的一员,(男子同志演唱团 "在海军"为其名曲)
The guy in the village people.
事实上 只有唱"在海军"时 他才是海军
Actually, he's only in the navy when they sing in the navy.
其余的时间 他只是杂役兵
The rest of the time, he's just in generic fatigues.
干吗?
What?
你挑起来的话题
You brought it up.
你没冲水
You didn't flush.
我没尿出来
I didn't pee.
男性 34岁 海军陆战队,刚结束两年在伊拉克的服役
Male.34.Just got out of the marines after two years in iraq.
据称患有慢性疲劳 关节疼痛
Admitted complaining of chronic fatigue, joint pains,
间歇性皮疹 以及咽喉痛
intermittent rashes, and sore throats.
他自己觉得患了海湾战争综合症
Thinks he has gulf war syndrome.
他怎么来这里,却不去VA(退伍军人管理局)?
Why is he here instead of the va?
因为Cuddy不想给他的有钱老舅口交
Because he has a rich uncle cuddy's trying to avoid fellating
他老舅不相信VA的"没有毛病"的诊断
who doesn't buy the va's diagnosis of "nothing's wrongatosis.
VA是对的
" The va's right.
没什么海湾战争综合症
There's no such thing as gulf war syndrome,
尤其是在从没参加过海湾战争的人身上
especially in veterans who've never served in the gulf war.
两场战争 一个地方
Different war, same place.
1990年在那儿的 还是在那儿
Whatever was there in 1990 is still there.
那里的东西能让你进棺材
What's there can send you home in a pine box,
但不可能让你回家三个月之后生病
but it can't get you sick three months after you've gotten home.
那成千上万的士兵都是在捏造症状?
What, so thousands of soldiers are lying about their symptoms?
你派七十万人去夏威夷度假,也会有人病着回家
You send 700,000 people on vacation to hawaii,,some are gonna come back sick.
不代表那是潜水呼吸管引起的
Doesn't mean it was caused by snorkeling.
他是对的 研究表面不论是否参加过海湾战争
He's right.The studies all show the same pattern of symptoms in veterans
那些退伍军人的症状都是一样的
who were sent to the gulf and those who weren'T.
就这样了 你信她却不信我?
That's it?You believe her but not me?
坚持你自己的意见 Chase
Stick to your guns, chase.
光因为没有一个统一症状不代表
Just 'cause there isn't a single unifying symptom doesn't mean
没有问题
there isn't something going on.
可能对每个人的影响都不一样
It could just affect everyone differently.
你认为这家伙有海湾战争综合症?
You think this guy has gulf war syndrome?
当然不是
'Course not.
他很抑郁 他想得到残疾证明
He's depressed, and he's looking for a disability check.
最可能的情况是因为他明白了
Most likely because he's just realized that knowing
能用六种语言求爱和用眼窝开啤酒
how to barter for sex in six languages and open a beer bottle
算不上什么可炫耀的本事
with your eye socket are not the most marketable skillS.
你为什么接这件病例?
why'd you take this ca?
因为一个优秀的科学家不断地自疑
Because a good scientist continually questions his own theories and assumptions.
Cuddy逼他的
Cuddy's maki him.
我现在就来逼你
Now I'm making you.
做个全身检查 重新验血检查艾滋病
Do a full physical. Recheck his blood for hiv,
丙肝 疟疾 血吸虫病 以及鲍式不动杆菌
hep c, malaria, schistosomiasis, and "t strain" A.
来确认VA的人眼睛没走神
Baumannii just to make sure the va's dotted their eyes.
然后找出他去过的每一家医院和诊所
And find out every hospital and clinic he's ever visited,
居住过的每个城市,以及他是不是上过电视
every city he's ever lived in, and...whether he's ever been on tv.
上电视?
Tv?
可能是神经学上的问题
Problem could be nrological.
人人都知道 看电视会变傻
Everyone knows tv rots your brain.
一般来说我掌心和脚底的情况最糟糕
It's usually the worst on my palms and the bottoms of my feet.
到处长满黑点
I get these black dots all over.
我什么都没看见
I don't see anything.
一会儿有一会儿没
It comes and goes.
你确定不是刮伤和乌青?
You sure it's not just scrapes and bruises?
我知道皮疹和乌青的区别
I know the difference between a rash and a bruise.
有时候那要比你想象的难辨别
sometimes it's harder than you realize to distinguish between the two.
很明显你健身
You obviously exercise.
我的问题不是健身引起的
My problems aren't caused by my workouts.
但你的确健身 从你的样子看来,练得还很勤
But you do work out, and by the look of you, pretty strenuously.
通常那样的人是不会
That's not usually the case with patients
抱怨慢性疲劳和关节疼痛的
whose principal complaint is chronic fatigue and joint pain.
我在海军陆战队服役12年
I was in the marines for 12 years.
我已经习惯每天健身
I'm used to doing pt every day.
我能忍受疼痛 不代表我不疼
Just because I can push through the pain doesn't mean it's not there.
听着 我们不是不相信你
listen, we're not saying we don't believe you.
幸亏不是如此
The hell you aren'T.
只是要查清楚具体问题
We just need to be specific about what exactly the problems are.
我每晚睡十个小时 但还是一直觉得累
I sleep ten hours a night, but I feel tired all the time.
我不断咳嗽 长皮疹 喉咙痛
I constantly get coughs, rashes, sore throats.
我膝盖和臀部关节疼得像有人往里灌沙
My knees and hips feel like someone poured sand in my joints.
我腿上有奇怪的麻刺感
I get these weird tingling sensations in my legs.
有时候 会发冷
Sometimes, they're cold.
有时候 又似乎血液都在沸腾
Other times, feels like my blood is boiling.
够具体了吗?
Specific enough?
看着 我不管你们叫它什么...
Look, I don't care what you guys call it--
海湾战争综合症 伊拉克热,还是干脆未知怪病一号
gulf war syndrome, iraq fever, or just crappy sickness X.
我只想有人能找出问题来,然后治好它
I just want someoneto figure out what it is so they can cure it.
除了关节处的假象疼痛
Except for the supposed pain in his joints,
剩余症状没有一个目前是明显的
none of the other symptoms he's complaining about are currently evident.
除了他健身后饮水过多 造成缺钾
Besides low potassium probably caused by him over hydrating after working out,
他的血液检查都正常
his blood work's all normal.
缺钾也肯可能是他被派往伊拉克前
Low potassium could also probably be caused by the experiments or vaccines in
注射的抗生化武器疫苗导致的
anti-chemical warfare pills he was given before he deployed to iraq.
更不用提那国家遍地都是
Not to mention the fact that whole country's littered with
上百吨的放射性贫铀弹碎片
hundreds of tons of radioactive shrapnel from depleted uranium munitions.
你在法国上的医学院?
Did you go to medical schoolin france?
他尿液里没有铀的痕迹
There's no trace of uraniumin his urine.
而且他在两年前注射疫苗
And he was given the vaccines and meds two years ago
而且没有过敏或者副作用
without any allergic or adverse reaction.
他当过模特吗?
Has he ever done any modeling?
我们忘了问
We forgot to ask.
应该把他的尿液送到列斯特大学去
We should send his urine to the university of leicester.
那里有位教授开发了,更精确的铀检测技术
There's a professor there who's developed,a more advanced screening technique for uranium.
如果含量低到我们检测不到的话
If the levels are too low for us to detect,
那么也不会造成什么伤害
they're way too low to cause any damage.
你去哪里?
Where you goin'?
这边
This way.
你们有发现关于他上电视,或者其他媒体的情况吗?
Did you find out about any television or other media exposure?
你真的在意 还是你想浪费医院资源
do you really care? Or are you just trying to waste hospital resources
来报复Cuddy逼你接这个病例?
to get back at cuddy for making you take the case?
我当然在意
Of course I care.
这么说太没良心了
What a horrible thing to say.
上lexisnexis数据库搜索一下,找一份他的信用记录
Do a lexisnexis search.Get a copy of his credit report.
在给他吃根香蕉 (补充钾),让他出院转去看心理医生 之前或之后?
Before or after we tell him to eat a banana and discharge him with a psych referral?
我说之前
I say before.
在两者之间 给他做个多导睡眠图
And I say in-between,give him a polysomnogram.
睡眠呼吸暂停症会导致慢性疲劳和妄想症
Sleep apnea can cause chronic fatigue and paranoia.
找找他去哪儿夏令营
Find out where he went to summer camp.
你没事吧?
Are you okay?
没事 早上咖啡喝太多了
Yeah, it's just a little too much coffee this morning.
我们刚才...是送你去厕所吗?
Were we...walking you to the bathroom?
希望如此
I wish.
Wilson刚才在里面
Wilson was just in there.
这两家伙知道我在说什么
These guys know what I'm talking about.
那是他第三轮快速眼动了 他的呼吸完全正常
that's his third rem cycle, and his breathing's completely normal.
他的睡眠没有任何问题
There's obviously nothing wrong with his sleep pattern.
不过不是铀 那就肯定是其它某种毒素
if it's not uranium, it's gotta be some other sort of toxin.
或者根本没毛病
Or nothing at all.
你是真希望他有问题,还是只希望Foreman是错的?
You really thinkthere's something wrong,,or do you just want foreman to be wrong?
都是
Both.
好吧 不是他的睡眠问题
Well, it's not his sleep pattern.
如果你真认为是毒素 明早做个肝脏活检
If you really think it's a toxin, you can do a liver biopsy in the morning.
我们不能走
We can't leave.
如果不监控整个过程,House不会接受出来的结果
If we don't monitor the whole test, house won't accept the results.
他就会让我们重做一遍
He'll just make us do it over.
完全正常的多导睡眠图,不需要两个医生来监控
It doesn't take two doctors to monitor,what's clearly gonna bea normal polysomnogram.
哦 那你是想让我留守?
Oh, so you want me to stay?
是你觉得有问题的啊
You're the one who thought there was something wrong.
我从没说过是睡眠失调
I never said it wasa sleep disorder.
你要掷硬币决定?
You wanna flip for it?
走吧走吧
Just go.
哦 拜托
Oh, come on.
别闹小孩子脾气
Don't be a baby.
好吧 我也留下
Fine. I'll stay.
你知道我们可以做点什么
You know what we could do.
- 这里?,- 为什么不行?
- Here?,- Why not?
周围都是有床的空房间
We're surrounded by empty rooms with beds in them.
是啊 还有摄像头呢
Yeah, and video cameras too.
关掉就行
So we turn 'em off.
就怕House或者Foreman进来看见我们
That's all I need is house or foreman walking in on us.
钥匙在我们这儿
We have the keys.
不行
No.
他醒过来怎么办?
What if he wakes up?
好吧
All right.
随你便
Suit yourself.
见鬼!
Damn it!
人呢?
hello?
外面有人吗?
Is anybody out there?
我想这里面出问题了!
I think there's a problem in here!
怎么了?
What's wrong?
你什么意思 怎么了 你没闻到吗?
What do you mean, what's wrong? You don't smell that?
什么味道都没有 John
Nothing smells, john.
你开玩笑吧 臭死了
Are you kidding me? It's disgusting.
你以为这样多久了 等等
How long have you thought--wait.
张嘴
Open your mouth.
味道不在房间里 在你嘴里
Smell's not in the room.It's in your mouth.
怎么了?
What's going on?
好问题
Good question.
怎么?
What?
你关于"没有毛病"的判断是错的
you were wrong about the "nothing's wrongatosis.
你可以假装疲劳和关节疼痛
" You can fake fatigue and joint paint,
但是你装不了嘴里的细菌性阴道炎
but you can't fake bacterial vaginosis in your mouth.
他的嘴都碰过哪儿?
where's his mouth been?
他说一年多没给别人口交过了
Says he hasn't performed oral sex on anyone in over a year.
自私的混蛋
Selfish bastard.
再没有和别人在一起,自从女朋友甩了他
Because he hasn't been with anyone since his last girlfriend dumped him
因为他第二次被派往伊拉克
and after he deployed to iraq the second time.
自私的娘们!
Selfish bitch!
可以排除艾滋病 糖尿病等所有内分泌失调疾病
We've ruled out hiv, diabetes, and any other endocrine abnormality.
可能是自身免疫 干燥症减少唾液分泌
Could be autoimmune; sjoegren's decreases salivary flow,
形成了细菌的温床
creates a hospitable home for bacteria.
不是 他眼睛和输泪管都正常
No, his eyes and tear ducts are fine.
他上一个女朋友是谁?
Who was his last girlfriend?
我们会...马上去查的
yeah, we'll...get right on that.
慢性疲劳 关节疼痛,以及机会性感染说明是癌症
Chronic fatigue, joint pain, and opportunistic infection spells cancer.
可能是淋巴癌
Probably lymphoma.
我们应该活检他的扁桃体和下颌下淋巴结
We should biopsy his tonsillar and submandibular lymph nodes.
是癌症
Right about cancer.
但不是淋巴癌
Wrong about lymphoma.
除非他的淋巴结是浮肿的
Unless you're simply hiding the fact that his lymph nodes are swollen.
让Wilson活检他的唾液腺
Get wilson to biopsy his salivary glands.
他有腮腺癌
He's got parotid cancer.
然后查出他到底泡过谁
And see if you can get to the truth about who he's been dating.
海军陆战队员不可能一整年"兵不刃血"
No way a marine goes a year without getting some blood on his bayonet.
不是性病
It's not an std.
- 你刚说...,- 做就是了
- You just said-,- just do it.
抗生素至少能减轻感染
the antibiotics should at least relieve the infection,
也能减少你嘴里的味道
also reduce the odor and taste in your mouth.
不够快
Not soon enough.
好吧
All right.
你会有点灼痛感
You're gonna feel a little burn.
要知道 我从来没沾过
You know,I never even dipped.
嚼烟草 我们那里除我之外每个人都嚼
Chewing tobacco. Practically everyone in my unit did but me.
我很惧怕癌症
I was so paranoid about cancer.
如果是腮腺癌,早期诊断出来 还是可以治愈的
Well, if it's parotid cancer, it's very treatable if diagnosed early.
我妈妈得癌症
My mom had cancer.
所以我知道早期诊断,是指在有严重症状之前
Which is why I know that diagnosing cancer early means,before there's any serious symptoms.
这尝起来绝对像严重的症状
Certainly tastes like a pretty serious symptom, you know?
检查之后会知道更多
We'll know more after the test.
如果他是想浪费时间来和Cuddy捣乱
if he was just trying to mess with cuddy for wasting his time,
那从病人显现症状开始就该停了
this would have stopped as soon as the patient started exhibiting actual symptoms.
问题是 为什么他要浪费时间?
So the question is, why is he wasting our time?
或者他是在浪费时间吗?
Or is he wasting our time?
你觉得他要这家伙的信用记录,有医学上的理由吗?
You think he's got a medical reason for asking for the guy's credit report?
我不觉得
I don'T.
那家伙醒来的时候你们俩去哪儿了?
Where were you twowhen the guy woke up?
呃 我们只是...出去一会儿
Uh, we just-- stepped out for a second.
去干吗?
To do what?
去...冲咖啡
To...get a coffee.
我们熬了一整晚
We'd been up most of the night.
他只是要确认我们有完整记录
He's just pushing to make sure we have a complete history.
若不就是我们漏了什么,应该已经有答案
Obviously, we're missing something, or we'd have the answer.
你回来的时候手上没咖啡
You didn't have any coffee when you came back.
好吧好吧
All right, already.
我们承认 被你发现了
We confess, you caught us.
我们溜到一个实验房间里去做爱了
We snuck into one of the sleep lab rooms to have sex.
不该在工作时做那样的事 我们很抱歉
We shouldn't have done it while we were supposed to be working, and we're sorry.
可以继续了吗?
Now can we move on?
在你干Chase之前 House会干Wilson
House'll do wilson before you do chase.
不 在我上Chase之前,你会上了House以及Wilson
No, you would do house and wilson before i do chase.
可以回到工作来了吗?
Now can we get back to work?
她有上过我的
She did me once.
她那时磕药了!
She was stoned!
活检不是决定性的
Biopsy's inconclusive.
在附加血检结果出来之前,我会做个涎管X线片
I'm gonna do a sialogram while we wait for the results,from the additional blood work.
不用急
No hurry.
也许到了这个境况 我们什么也做不了
Probably nothing we can do at this point anyway.
只要癌细胞没有扩散
As long as the cancer hasn't spread.
他的口水都是臭的
He's spitting stink.
你应该多关注下活人
You should focus on the living.
我需要一张处方
I need a prescription.
我刚给你写过处方
I just wrote you a prescription.
那是维克丁的
For vicodin.
我需要阿呋唑嗪(治疗前列腺增生)
I need alfuzosin.
不 你不需要
No, you don'T.
你想出来 在哪里碰到海军陆战队员了吗?
Have you figured out where you met your marine?
什么?
What?
哦 那个
Oh, that.
没怎么想
Haven't really thought about it.
我尿不出来
I can't pee.
你记不住他 对吧?
You can't remember him, can you?
我尿不出来
I can't pee.
那就别吃维克丁了
So stop taking the vicodin.
我既想尿尿又不想疼痛
I wanna pee and not be in pain.
你为什么不去睡觉?
Why don't you go to sleep?
我睡觉的时候不会尿尿
I don't pee when I'm asleep.
也许他会再度进入你梦乡 给你个地址
Maybe you'll dream about him again. Maybe he'll give you an address.
我已经三天没撒尿了
I haven't peed in three days.
我读到过 大脑在快速眼动期解决问题
I read that rem sleep is the brain's way of working out problems.
受益匪浅
Very useful.
听到我说的话了吗?
Did you hear what I just said?
是的 你撒谎,为了避免谈及你着魔了
Yeah, you lied because you want to avoid talking about your obsession.
我没有着魔
I'm not obsessing.
为什么不直接问他呢?
Why don't you just ask him?
我三天没撒尿了!
I haven't peed in three days!
那你都死了
You'd be dead.
我没算间歇性滴出来的尿液
I'm not counting intermittent drips.
你会痛苦不堪
You'd be in agony.
昨天4点前后我已经痛苦不堪过了
I passed agony yesterday around 4:00.
他的母亲 兄弟 叔父和密友都确认
His mother, brother, uncle, and best friend all confirm
他一年多没约会了
he hasn't had a date in over a year.
说明这不是性病
Which means it's not an std.
如果发现跟医学有关的问题 传呼我
If you come up with something medically relevant, page me.
你让我怎么跟他说呢 实话实说?
What did you want me to tell him, the truth?
不 也犯不着让他信服
No.You didn't haveto be so convincing.
别担心 我会补偿给你的
Don't worry.I'll make it up to you.
这事已经控制不住了
This is getting out of control.
别板着脸
Don't pout.
病人受到感染醒来时,我们正在翻云覆雨
Our patient woke up with an infection while we were getting our rocks off.
你想停下吗?
Do you want to stop?
不
No.
但我不想被人抓到
But, uh, I don't want to get caught either.
你以为我想?
You think I do?
在睡眠研究实验室里,你明显是故意不肯压低嗓门
You certainly didn't go out of your way to keep the volume down,when we were in the sleep lab.
我控制不住
I couldn't help that.
我为什么希望被人抓到呢?
Why would i wanna get caught?
也许想引起House的醋意
Maybe you wanna give house a reason to be jealous.
我对House没感觉了
I'm over house.
这不过是简单的性
All this is is uncomplicated sex.
别小题大做
Don't try to make it more than that.
我再不会在工作时偷欢了
I'm not doing it at work anymore.
很好
Fine.
去吃午饭吗?
Wanna go grab some lunch?
我认为口服避孕药应该是上策
I think the pillis the way to go.
我们还没弄破过避孕套 谢天谢地,但总会发生的
We haven't had a condom break yet, thank god, but it's bound to happen.
特别是以我们这种方式
Especially the way we've been doing it.
如躺针毡?
On a bed of nails?
不 他不是什么怪人
No.He's not kinky.
他只是...欲海无边
He's just...insatiable.
害我早上的课 几乎从没准时过
I can barely make it to any of my morning classes.
你抽烟吗?
You smoke?
绝不
No way.
别晃了!
Stop it!
对不起
Sorry.
以前患过高血压 血块凝结或中风吗?
Any history of hypertension, blood clots, strokes?
没有 我非常健康 就有点强迫症
Nope. Besides my ocd, I'm fit as a fiddle.
你有强迫症?
You have ocd?
你看不出来吗?
Duh. Can't you tell?
除大量喝水外还有其它强迫性行为吗?
Any other compulsions besides drinking massive amounts of water?
没有了 就此而已 谢天谢地
No, that's it, thank god.
我的心理医生说症状本可能严重得多
My therapist saysit could be a lot worse.
你半夜也爬起来喝水?
You get up in the middle of the night to drink?
是的 隔几个小时就喝
Yeah, every couple of hours.
那你的心理医生就是个白痴
Well, then your therapist is an idiot.
人无意识时不会有强迫症
Unconscious people don't have ocd.
但可能得了尿崩症
They can, however, have diabetes insipidus.
不可能 我一直吃糖来着
That's impossible. I eat candy all the time.
另一种糖尿病
Different kind of diabetes.
源于垂体受损
This kind is caused by a banged-up pituitary.
你显然享受强迫症 而不抗争
You're obviously more of a lover than a fighter.
我猜要么是车祸要么...
I'm guessing eithera car accident or...
要么就是你脑壳撞上了平衡木
you cracked your skull on the balance beam.
你怎么知道?
How'd you know?
很简单 屁股漂亮 胸脯扁平
Easy. Nice ass, no boobs.
手掌象港口工人一样粗糙
You got palms like a longshoreman.
等在这儿 你得做下断层扫描
Wait here. You need a cat scan.
哦 我的天
Oh, my god.
别担心 这不过意味着,你要吃两种荷尔蒙补充剂 而不是一种
Don't worry, just means you'll be taking two hormone supplements instead of one.
好了 这次你会感到有点压力
Okay, this time you're gonna feel a little pressure.
我们在注入造影剂
We're injecting the contrast material.
你能把音量调大点吗?
Could you turn up the music?
当然可以
Sure.
现在为止状况良好
Looks pretty goodso far.
还是听不清楚
Still can't hear it that well.
现在能听清了吗?
Can you hear it now?
John?
John!
John 能听到我说话吗?
John, can you hear me?
还是没有...解脱?
Still no...relief?
会解脱的
I t relief.
只是撒不出尿
Just got no pee.
如果药没起效 也许你得使用导尿管
If the pills didn't work, you may need a catheter.
你来不是为了跟我谈我的尿
You didn't come here to talk to me about my pee.
发生什么事了?
What's going on?
好吧 他得了癌
He's got cancer, all right.
但不在他的唾腺里
But it's not in his salivary glands.
而是在他大脑里
It's in his brain.
情况很糟
And it's bad.
至少有六个瘤 也许更多
At least six tumors, maybe more.
他丧失了听力
He lost his hearing.
很可能下一步就是丧失视力
His sight's probably next.
死亡多半紧随其后
Death is probably next.
他不可能一星期就长出这么多瘤
no way he could have grown all these in a week.
就是新长的
they can't be older.
退伍军人医院不可能一点没查出来
The va couldn't have missed all these.
也许不是没查出来 而是搞混淆了
Maybe they didn't miss them, just mixed 'em up.
将他的片子跟其他病人的搞混了
Switched his films with another patient's by mistake.
也许 意味着某个可怜的傻瓜,在退伍军人医院 脑瓜被平白无故切开
Maybe. But it means some poor sap's getting,his melon sliced at the va for no reason.
而这个可怜的中士周末就会死
And this poor sergeant's gonna be dead by the end of the week.
你们两个去哪了?
Where have you two been?
吃午饭
lunch.
为什么 发生什么事了?
Why, what happened?
Wilson发现了些形成飞速 神秘莫测的,神奇脑瘤
Wilson's found some fast-growing, elusive, or magic brain tumors.
你们有发现吗?
What'd you find?
没什么 他说的是实话
Nothing. He's telling the truth.
- 关于什么?,- 一切
- About what?,- about everything.
他住过哪儿 跟谁约会过
Where he's lived, who he's dated.
除了忘记提他父亲有过胫骨骨裂
Besides forgetting to mention his dad's shin splits,
他的爷爷流鼻血和忘了还DVD
his granddad's nose bleeds and to return a few rented dvds,
其它一切都证实无误
everything he's told us has checked out.
你让他们对你的梦进行调查?
You have them researching your dream?
没有 我让他们调查我的病人
No.I have them researching my patient.
你梦见了病人?
You had a dream about a patient?
这个可怜家伙的脑袋长满了瘤,而你在查他的信用报告?
this poor guy's brain is riddled with tumors,,and you're checking his credit report?
来吧 我需要你们帮忙
Come on. I need you guys.
你们去哪儿?
Where are you going?
干我的活
To do my job.
他不是你的病人
He's not your patient.
现在是了 回家睡觉去吧
He is now. Go home and go to sleep.
也许你会梦见治疗晚期脑癌的灵丹妙药
Maybe you'll dream the cure to late-stage brain cancer.
他怎么样?
How is he?
死了
He's dead.
哦...上帝
Oh...god.
过不了几天就会死
At least, he will be in a few days.
问题是为什么?
The question is why?
唯一的解释是退伍军人医院搞砸了
The only explanation is that the va hospital screwed up.
绝对没有搞混 我让他们重新检查过
There was definitely no mix-up. I had them recheck.
是啊 政府机构又何须撒谎,掩盖致命误诊?
Yes. Why would a government agency lie to cover up a mistake that might have
反正在过去两年就想要他的命了
caused the death of a guy they'd been trying to kill for the last two years anyway?
他们没撒谎
They didn't lie.
你刚吞了两片维柯丁?
Did you just take two vicodin?
没有 这是抗抑郁药
No.It was an antidepressant.
我一见到你进屋 就得服两片
I was told to take two every time you walked into the room.
退伍军人医院对他做的大脑扫描图
The va scan of his brain.
没有肿瘤
No tumors.
是的 这显然证明某人脑袋里没长瘤
Yes, this is proof positive that someone didn't have tumors in their brain.
看到他左眼眶下的亮点没?
You see that bright spot below his left orbit?
这是20年前植入你的病人体内的钛夾
That is a titanium pin your patient had inserted 20 years ago.
除非你相信退伍军人医院,不小心把扫描图跟另一个人的搞混了
Unless you think the va happened to mix up his scans
那个人有一模一样的钛夾,否则他们就没搞错
with someone who had the exact same pin, they didn't screw up.
你呼我们?
You paged us?
为什么不照我说的,把他的尿样送去莱斯特大学呢?
Why didn't you send his urineto leicester like I told you?
因为你说了别送
Because you told me not to.
为什么你偏挑那一刻听我的话?
Why did you choose that moment to listen to me?
你觉得他的瘤跟贫铀有关?
You think depleted uranium might have something to do with his tumors?
只有辐射才能让瘤长得那么快
Radiation's the only thing that would make tumors grow that fast.
大量的辐射
High doses of radiation.
即便他拿贫铀弹当早餐
Even if he ate depleted uranium bullets for breakfast,
他吸收的辐射也不如
he still would have been exposed to less radiation than
我们过去两天给他的多
we've given him in the last two days.
不管怎样 送去吧
Do it anyway.
你则去把他叔叔叫回来
And you,call his uncle back.
看他是否带他侄子去过,医院举办的晚会或筹款活动
Find out if he ever brought his nephew to any hospital parties or fundraisers.
不 除非你给我个理由
No.Not until you give me a reason.
因为...我是你老板
Because...I'm your boss.
合理的理由
A rational reason.
或至少承认你没理由
Or at least admit that you don't have one.
我的膀胱胀满了 我可不怕把这当理由
I've got a full bladder, and I'm not afraid to use it.
但显然你害怕发现,你无法合理解释的事
But you are, apparently, afraid of discovering something,you can't rationally explain.
闭嘴!
Shut up!
照吩咐的去做
Do what you're told.
Cuddy和Wilson也许不用听我的话,但你不听也得听
Cuddy and wilson may not have to listen to me, but you do.
这到底是怎么回事?
What the hell was that all about?
我不在乎
I don't care.
也觉得没必要去问他八个私人问题
Which is why I didn't feel the need to ask him eight personal questions.
我对他已经没感觉了
I'm over him.
不过是在观察
Just making an observation.
好吧 时刻准备了
all right, ready whenever you are.
准备好了
I'm ready.
等等
Wait a minute.
放大
Zoom in.
我看不到 你肯定坐标没错?
I don't see it. You sure you got the right coordinates?
是的 位置正确
Yeah, she's in the right place.
Z轴上沿ac-pc线向上移10毫米
Go 10 millimeters above the ac-pc line on the z access.
Z轴往ac-pc线上移10毫米
ten mil above ac-pc on Z.
它不见了
It's not there anymore.
你肯定机架角设定得正确?
Are you sure you got the gantry angle right?
是的 我肯定
Yeah, I'm sure.
瘤不见了
It's not there.
消失了
It disappeared.
六个瘤不会莫名其妙就消失
Six tumors don't just disappear.
除非本来就没有
Unless they were never there to begin with.
退伍军人医院没搞砸
The va didn't screw up.
也许是别人
Maybe someone else did.
也许是"自以为是"医生
Maybe it was dr.Self-righteous.
我看到了瘤
I saw the tumors.
也没有搞混
There was no mix-up.
也许是手术室的便携式光谱仪出问题了
maybe there's something wrong with the portable imagerin the O.R.
让脑组织纤毫毕现
something that would cause it to show brain tissue in perfect detail
而对赘生性组织视若无物?
but completely miss neoplastic tissue?
那么一开始就没有瘤
Then they were never tumors to begin with.
我告诉你了 我看到...
I told you, I saw--
我知道 你看到了形似瘤的物质
I know, you saw something that looked like tumors.
我们都看到了 我们看错了
We all did. We were all wrong.
也许他没得癌症
Well, maybe he doesn't have cancer.
也许是他的脑部感染引发了多发性脓疡
Maybe he has a brain infection that's causing multiple abscesses.
然后奇迹般的自愈了
That miraculously healed.
不 是被抗生素治好的,治他口腔细菌性阴道炎的
No, they were healed by the antibiotics,we're giving him for the vaginosisin his mouth.
要是感染的话 怎么血液检查没发现
If it's an infection, why didn't it show up in his blood work?
我也不知道 到现在为止
I don't know. Yet.
Wilson医生 有麻烦了
Dr.Wilson, we have a problem.
你们都干什么了!
what did you do?!
我的腿没知觉了!
I can't feel my legs!
你们做了什么?
What'd you guys do?
John 镇静点 我们还没做手术
John, calm down. We didn't even operate.
会不会是麻醉药的残余作用--
Could it be a residual effect of--
我的腿动不了了
I can't move my legs!
不是麻醉药的作用
it's not the anesthesia.
John 我们会搞清楚你的病情
John, john, we're gonna figure out what's wrong with you.
首先要知道一件事--
First we need to know one thing--
你有没有拍过色情片?
have you ever appeared in any pornos?
慢性疲劳 喉咙痛,皮疹 散发恶臭的嘴
Chronic Fatique, sore throats, rashes, putrid Discharge mouth
脑部多处脓肿 听力丧失,最后很重要的一点 下肢瘫痪
Mult abscesses in the brain, Hearing loss,lower limb paralysis.
真是给了我们很多提示
This certainly gives us plenty of clues
可能是某种感染
It could be sort of infection
迅速改善大脑病情,却恶化了他的耳朵和腿?
some improving his brain and getting worse his ears and legs.
可能是感染加癌症,新生瘤会抑制免疫系统 引发其他症状
Could be infection and cancer. the neoplastic syndrome could depress the immune system and cause the  other syptomes
你的理论是基于生物活检的阴性结果?
Mmm. You're basing your theory on negative biopsy and****world
还有一开始就不存在的肿瘤
Tumors never there to begin with
那你的理论难道基于他最喜欢的餐馆?
and what are you gonna base your theory on--his favorite restaurants?
被我说对了
I was right.
他正随尿排出废铀
He's excreting depleted uranium in his urine.
应该开始静脉注射等渗的碳酸氢钠
We should start him on an iv infusion of isotonic sodium bicarbonate.
- 不是废铀,- 是你要求--
- It's not depleted uranium.,- You're the one--
是在我们考虑癌症时要求做这个检查,现在不考虑癌症了
who asked for the test when we were thinking cancer. We no longer are.
废铀不仅会引起细胞变异
Depleted uranium doesn't just cause cells to mutate.
也能导致细胞死亡
It can cause cell death as well.
不会导致脊髓细胞死亡
Not spinal cord cells.
除非剂量大到先杀死所有其它细胞
At least, not until the dose is high enough to kill all his other cells first.
所以你的意思是尿中的放射性铀是无关的
So you're saying the radioactive uranium in his urine is irrelevant.
太阳是放射性的
The sun's radioactive.
地球是放射性的
The earth is radioactive.
这个医院也充满了放射
This hospital is filled with radiation.
问题不在于哪里 而是多大剂量
The issue is not where it is but how much there is and
以及在某人的脊髓上能造成多大伤害
what damage that amount could cause in someone's spinal cord.
我已经清楚声明了---
And as I already stated quite clearly--
明白了 我们都是傻瓜
got it. We're all idiots.
你的理论是什么?
What's your theory?
- 给我你的钥匙,- 为什么?
- Gimme your keys.,- Why?
你试过膀胱胀大还骑摩托车吗?
You ever tried riding a motorcycle with a distended bladder?
继续用抗生素
Keep him on antibiotics.
每小时检查他的听力和瘫痪情况
Check his hearing and paralysis every hour.
所以你想我们什么都不做
so you basically want us to do nothing.
不 基本上 我想什么都不做
No, I basically wanna do nothing.
我要你们继续给他用抗生素,每小时检查听力和瘫痪情况
I want you to keep him on antibiotics and check his hearing and paralysis every hour.
等一下 你不能现在回家
wait, you can't go home now.
事实上 我现在得回家
Actually, I have to go home now.
我两天前就该睡了
It's two days past my bedtime.
House 他需要你帮助
House, he needs your help.
而我需要睡眠
And I need sleep.
这就是大脑解决难题的方法
Hey, it's the brain's way of working out problems
当头脑清醒时解决不了时 你说的
that the conscious mind can't solve during the day, remember?
现在呢?
Now?
不 没感觉
No. Nothing.
我要死了 是吗?
I'm gonna die, aren't I?
我们正在竭尽所能
we're doing all we can.
不 我们没有
no, we're not.
我们应该采用你提议的铀中毒的治疗
We should start treatment for the uranium toxicity like you said.
但是House--不在这儿
But house--isn't here.
如果House想参与这个病例--
if house wanted to be involved in the case--
如果他想用这种治疗方案
If he wanted us to start this treatment,
你上次提起时 他就会让我们用了
he would have told us to do it the last time you brought it up.
你有更好的主意?
You have a better idea?
没有
No.
那我们就用Chase的
Then we're going with chase'S.
我们有个主意
We have an idea.
告诉他别让管子缠在一起
tell him not to get the lines tangled.
滴注速度很慢 这条管子不能有纠结
The infusion is slow. We can't have any kinks in the line.
我也上过医学学校
I went to medical school too.
别让管子缠在一起
Don't tangle the lines!
把你的胳膊放在身上 就放胸前
Keep your arms on your body, above your heart.
我的胃没知觉了
I can't feel my stomach!
我感觉不到那个
I don't feel that.
我什么都感觉不到
I don't feel anything!
瘫痪在向上延伸
Paralysis is ascending.
如果继续下去 我们就要用呼吸机了
If it keeps going, we're gonna need a respirator.
什么 你们在说什么?
What? What are you saying?
你能呼吸吗?
Can you breathe?
呼吸困难吗?
Trouble breathing?
不 还没有
No.Not yet.
--在新泽西公园路91号出口发生车祸...
--Accident on the garden state parkway south bound at exit 91...
情况如何?
so, where were we?
昨晚睡得好吗?
You have a nice night?
不好
No.
瘫痪在向上延伸
The paralysis is ascending.
上次检查 已经接近横隔膜了
The last check, it was nearly to his diaphragm.
告诉我们一些事情
tells us something.
说明病情恶化了
means it's getting worse.
恶化也是提示
Worse is something.
说明不是铀引起
Also tells us it's not the uranium.
我们有考虑过铀吗?
Did we think it was?
我们用了碳酸钠让他排出废铀
We started him on sodium bicarb to try to flush the uranium out of his system.
好极了 现在他情况恶化也不能提示什么
Great. Now the fact that he's getting worse tells us nothing.
从没考虑过是铀
Never thought it was uranium.
就我们所知 排铀治疗是让他--
For all we know, the uranium treatment is what's making him--
碳酸钠滴注不会引起这作用--
a sodium bicarb infusion wouldn't have any effect on--
引起什么?
on what?
很难说没有影响
Kind of hard to say what it wouldn't have an effect on
如果连原始病因是什么都不知道
if you've no idea what's there to affect.
我们总得做点什么
We had to do something.
下次...试点会有用的办法
Well, next time...go with something that has a chance of working.
比如?
Like what?
在家里温暖舒适的床上,你想出什么高明的主意了吗?
You come up with some brilliant idea while,you're warm and cozy in your bed at home?
我们需要更多信息
We need more information.
你到底还要多少信息?
How much more information could you possibly want?
我们有从他曾祖父辈开始的家族病史
We have a medical history going all the way back to his great-grandparents.
- 非医疗史从,- 这还不够
- A non-medical history going-,- it's not enough.
我们能得到的就这些了
It's all we're gonna get.
想打赌吗?
Wanna bet?
谁批准碳酸钠滴注的?
Who approved a sodium bicarb infusion?
别看我 我在家里床上呢
Don't look at me. I was home in bed.
出什么事了?
What's wrong?
他昏迷了
he's unconscious.
他的皮肤没有颜色,血压和红细胞比容迅速下降
His skin has lost all color, and his bp and hematocrit are plunging.
- 他不过是用了碳酸钠--,- 他正在出血
- he was only on the sodium bicarb-,- he's bleeding out.
他不可能在出血 床上没有血
He can't be bleeding out. There's no blood in the bed.
好吧 他是内出血
Fine, he's bleeding in.
没有瘀伤或内出血的迹象
There's no sign of bruising or internal hemorrhaging.
瘫痪一定已经到了横隔膜
paralysis must have reached his diaphragm.
无法给血液供氧
He's not able to oxygenate his blood.
无法给血液供氧是因为他已经快没血了
He's not able to oxygenate his blood because he doesn't have any left.
没有证据--,这是唯一能解释--
there's no evidence-- it's the only thing that would explain--
没有理由失血的
there's no reason for blood loss.
一定有原因
There has to be a reason.
他需要输血 给我4单位的O阴性血 马上
He needs a transfusion. Get me 4 units of o negative.Stat!
抬起他的脚
Let's elevate his feet.
他不需要输血
He doesn't need a transfusion.
没人问你的意见
Nobody asked you.
事实上 你怎么会在这儿?
In fact, why are you even here?
很显然 因为你需要我帮忙
Because, obviously, you need my help.
出去
Get out.
House 他的血显然没有消失-
House, his blood obviously didn't just vanish into--
见鬼 这是什么东西?
what the hell is this?
肯定有人弄洒了什么
Somebody must have spilled something.
来个人给我4单位...
Somebody else should be getting me 4 units...
到底是什么?
what the hell is that?
有个裂缝的导尿管收集袋
It's a urine catheter collection bag with a rip in it--
它看起来像什么?
what the hell does it look like?
什么?
What?
不过是尿液而已 无菌的
It's just urine.It's sterile.
没人帮我拿血
No one's getting me blood.
为什么没人帮我拿血?
Why isn't anybody getting me blood?
你流鼻血了
You're bleeding.
House 你还好吗?
House, are you all right?
你怎么会在这儿?
Why are you even here?
我一直在这儿
I'm always here.
不 你不在
No, you're not.
一定有原因
There's a reason.
一定有
There has to be.
新泽西公园路发生事故
Incident on the garden state parkway...
情况怎样?
so.Where were we?
昨晚睡得好吗?
You have a nice night?
是 不错 谢谢关心
Yes, I did, thank you.
我猜比我们的病人好很多,他的血压和红血球比容在迅速下降
I'm guessing better than our patient,,probably due to his bpand hematocrit plunging.
你怎么会知道?
How'd you know?
答案一直都摆在我们面前,就像鼻子在脸上那样明显
the answer was staring right at us the whole time,,as plain as the nose on our faces.
或者他脸上的鼻子
Or the nose on his face.
发生什么事了 他说什么?
What's going on? What'd he say?
没有鼻毛 有灼烧疤痕
No hairs, and cauterization scars.
这意味着?
Which means?
他灼烧过这里
He had it cauterized.
你怎么能知道这个?
How could you know that?
因为这样才合理
Just makes sense.
他和祖父一样小时候鼻子常出血,毫无疑问 灼烧是为了阻止这个
Undoubtedly done to stop the same childhood nosebleeds,that plagued his grandfather.
毫无疑问 他们有遗传性,出血性毛细血管扩张症
Undoubtedly, because they were both born with hereditary hemorrhagic telangiectasia.
他在说什么?
What's he saying?
我在说你有遗传病 损害你的毛细血管
I'm saying you've got a genetic disease that's destroying your capillaries.
他们家以前从来没人被诊断出这病?
that no one in his family's ever been diagnosed with before?
一点不奇怪 通常一开始症状是--
Not surprising, since the most common initial symptoms--
皮疹和鼻子出血--
skin rashes and nose bleeds--
经常被视作小创伤或干燥天气的结果
are often written off as the result or minor trauma or dry weather.
但也可能是因为动脉静脉融合在一起
But they can also be the result of his arteries and veins merging together.
他很显然有动静脉畸形
He obviously has avms.
脊柱旁边的动静脉畸形引起瘫痪
Avm near the spine caused the paralysis.
肺上的动静脉畸形阻止了血液被过滤
Avm in his lungs prevented his blood from being filtered.
没过滤的血引起关节痛 疲劳,口腔和脑子里的感染
Dirty blood caused the joint pain, fatigue,,and the infections in his mouth and brain.
只要几个手术没什么不能清除的
Nothing that a few surgeries won't clear up.
对前面提到的都做血管造影
Get mr angiograms of the aforementioned.
海军陆战队没有隐瞒任何事 他隐瞒了
The marines weren't hiding anything. He was.
至少忘了提及他用止血棉
Or at least he forgot to mention his bloody tissue issue.
发生什么了?
What's going on?
他说了什么?
What'd he say?
看起来病例解决了 你的其它问题也好了
oh, looks like solving the case solved your other problem.
没什么灵药比得上幸福
There is no medicine like happiness.
或许还有欢笑
Except maybe laughter.
或者把橡胶管子推挤进尿道
Or rubber tubes shoved up your urethra.
你给自己插了尿管?
You cathed yourself?
除了刚开始的9到10英寸,实际上插管也没有那么糟糕
It's actually not that bad after the first, I don't know, nine or ten inches.
插管缓解了痉挛
Cath relieved the spasm.
我健康如初了
I'm as good as new.
当然 只不过是一次小小的痉挛
Of course. Just a minor spasmin a muscle you've been using multiple times
在一块你45年来 每天用好几次的肌肉上
a day without any problem for the past 45 years.
不是过度使用止痛药的严重副作用
Not a major side effect caused by the over-use of a particular narcotic pain killer.
是 我也这么想
Yeah, that was my thought too.
仍不予考虑减少使用某种药片的剂量
So...no reason to think about cutting back on your use of that particular pilL.
感谢上帝
Thank god.
事实上 是正常的三倍剂量
Actually, it was a triple dose of the good stuff that allowed me
才能让我睡一会觉 解决病例
to finally get some sleep and solve the case.
药片让我美梦成真
Pills made all my dreams come true.
你真是在睡觉时得到答案的?
You really got the answers in your sleep?
一个在睡觉时 另一个在冲澡时
Got one in my sleep. The other one I got in the shower.
我一直在想你
I've been thinking about you.
你撒谎了
You lied.
我没有
I didn't lie.
我只是选择不分享无关的事情
I simply chose not to share completely irrelevant facts.
比如你撒谎这种事
Like the fact that you lied.
怪不得我没法对上他的脸
No wonder I couldn't place his face.
在舞池里你都快把他的脸吞了
You were practically swallowing it on the dance floor.
我没有
I was not.
谈谈那个酷叔叔吧
Talk about the cool uncle.
他捐了钱 侄子可以尝甜头
He donates the money, and the nephew gets the write-off.
所谓甜头 是指他把你的脚踝搁在
And, of course, by write-off, I mean he gets to put your ankles--
这恰恰是为什么,我不提两年前的那次约会
this is exactly why I didn't mention our one date over two years ago.
因为我的T恤
Because of my t-shirt.
因为你是个讨厌的混蛋
Because you are an obnoxious ass.
因为你会用所有时间--
Because you would have spent the whole time--
真够聪明的
that's very smart.
因为这样 我就会全神贯注于病人
'Cause this way, I spent my whole time completely focused on the patient.
你怎么会记得他?
How did you even remember him?
我们在那个聚会上只出现了十分钟
We were only at that party for, like, ten minutes.
这是新的医疗计划吗?
Is this some new health plan?
为院长你服务 就能得到一年的免费医疗?
You service the dean of medicine, and you get free health care for a year?
你在笑什么?
Why are you smiling?
你记得他 是因为他和我交往过
You remembered him because he made out with me.
我认面孔很在行
I'm good with faces.
那么 这个计划 对别人开放吗?
So, this plan, is it open to anyone?
有没有定额自付?
Is there a co-pay?
你认脸一塌糊涂
You're lousy with faces.
别把这事扯到我身上
Don't make this about me.
这是你的耻辱
This is your humiliation.
私人房间的费用是多少?
So how much for private room coverage?
别再对我念念不忘
Get over me.
得了吧 你雇我--
Gimme a break.You hired me--
因为你是一个,连血库都不愿意雇用的好医生
'cause you're a good doctor who couldn't get himself hired at a blood bank,
所以我捡了便宜
so i got you cheap.
你肯给所有我要的
You gave me everything I asked for,
是因为有一天晚上 我给你所有--
because one night I gave you everything you--
别以为我没看就盯着我的臀部
stop staring at my ass when you think I'm not looking,
刚好出现在我约会的餐馆
showing up at restaurants where I happen to be on a date,
冲澡时幻想我
and fantasizing about me in the shower.
船早就开走了 House
That ship sailed long ago, house.
放手吧
Get over it.
如果船指的还是你的臀部
If you're still referring to your ass,
我觉得 "巨型油轮开走了",会是更准确的比喻
I think "that super-tanker sailed" would be the more precise metaphor.
不好意思 我在找个大的垃圾桶
sorry. I was lookingfor an extra-large trash can.
他从什么时候起也打扫了?
Since when does he clean anything up?